

Watchara Hongkim

Birthdate: 26 August 1992

Email: watchara.hongkim@gmail.com

Tel: 09-1704-7733

Address: 459/74 Rama2 road, Bangmod sub-district, Jomthong district, Bangkok 10150

I am frontend developer, and I am passionate and dedicated to my work. With 7 years' experience as a web developer, I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I enjoy every step of the design process, from discussion and collaboration.

Skill & Proficiencies

Computer Languages: Javascript, Typescript, HTML, CSS

Frameworks: ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, React Native(Expo), Redux, Recoiljs, Styled-Components, Bootstrap

Others: Docker, Docker compose, Version Control (GIT), Agile/Scrum, Linux, OSX, Firebase, Firestore, AWS, MongoDB, Redis

Experiences

Rovula Co.,Ltd

Frontend Developer

April 2021 - Present

- Developed a dashboard website that manages data of underwater robots.
- Developed a website that handles video overlay for livestream.
- Developed a website for viewing real-time (livestream) data from underwater robots.

Punpromotion Co.,Ltd

Software Engineer

November 2018 - March 2021

- Changed the company's website from CMS to ReactJS. Knowledge of planning, design database design, website, API, and Cloud Server.
- Strong understanding of ReactJS. Experience of using React Native, Next.js, Redux, Responsive website will be a considerable bonus.
- Ability to manage backend using ExpressJS.
- Basic understanding of API security.
- Knowledge of NoSQL (Redis, MongoDB, Firebase, Firestore) and SQL.
- Experience of deploying on a cloud server (AWS, Digital Ocean).
- Good understanding of SEO principles.
- Familiar with deadline, communicate with other teams.
- Good understanding of software development approach using Agile methodology.
- Ability to share knowledge with less experienced developers and bringing the experience to make good decisions.

Kratos Co.,Ltd

Programmer

September 2016 - October 2018

develop a website on basis of business needs and requirements. develop by PHP, React connect an API. design, develop a real-time website with firebase, and display on live stream system.

Educations

- Bachelor Degree at Information Technology, Faculty of Informatics, Burapha University
- High School, Wichienmatu School

References

- https://watcharah.netlify.app
- https://github.com/timenakrab